Talking about how this group that I'm involved with here in Arizona get started.
The group was originally started before I was here in town by just a few people who wanted to get together and put on some plays.
They were reforming in a community building over in Cottonwood, the town next door in the old town section of Cottonwood, and they named the group Old Town Players.
They put on 3 productions a year I believe.
Very small productions, not very many props, not much of a set, but they were well received.
There was really no other live theater here in the Verde Valley.
Gradually the group got larger and they decided they really should have a board of directors governing things, keeping track of the money, and planning and that sort of thing, so they appointed a board of directors.
The group continued to grow.
Then it became to difficult to schedule the shows in the building they were in so they moved over here to the Clarkdale clubhouse.
It's a community building here in Clarkdale, Arizona.
This has worked quite a bit better for us.
The building isn't as heavily used.
We need to have it not just for when we're performing the play but for rehearsals and building the set and all sorts of things.
Then as you go along, you kind of want things to go up a notch or two.
There's time to do that and we're about where we should be right now.